Oye!
Ruff!
[SPEAKER_01]: No, the snake was fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a male.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, sort of.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a male, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's quite clean as well, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no, there are some ticks.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm gonna go... Yeah, some ticks here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who is barking?
[SPEAKER_00]: All of them?
[SPEAKER_01]: All of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thandi was cornering it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Timmy was flanking it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pepper was quite animated.
[SPEAKER_01]: He came down crashing down that rock.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he really wants to... How about you let go of my arm now?
[SPEAKER_01]: That skin shed you found?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's this one, definitely.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because there are pieces that are left around the eyes.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, that's why it looks so clean.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a fresh shed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Timmy, don't mess around.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't mess around.
[SPEAKER_01]: Snake shed, freaking her out.
It's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yuri!
[SPEAKER_01]: Come here, boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: What you doing there?
That's it, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm trying to make this higher here, so they don't jump.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, when they get very keen.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'll stick those sticks, those plants.
[SPEAKER_01]: Plant the trees around at the back.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, they'll do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, they will do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It stops.
[SPEAKER_01]: And visually as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: It would block the ideas of getting out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Come over.
[SPEAKER_00]: Come on, boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good boy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Chavo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sit, sit, sit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good, good, good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_01]: Good boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rose?
[SPEAKER_01]: Come here, come here, old lady.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, good girl.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jabu.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know you had enough.
[SPEAKER_01]: You had enough.
[SPEAKER_00]: Timmy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Pepper?